[{"answer": "Do you want to go, my friend", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What have you got", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, give me a couple of days to get used to the idea. I'll be all right", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I don't want to go to this bachelor party", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, he was funny", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, they were", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " You fellows going to that place's party tonight", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No. my friend already hooked me for four bucks for that place's present. This dinner is going to cost another couple of good dollars", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No. my friend already hooked me for four bucks for that place's present. This dinner is going to cost another couple of good dollars", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You ain't going", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It looks like nobody's going to that place's bachelor party", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, I'm not going", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You ain't going", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend's going to be mad", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Man, you were going strong with that girl. You could have scored. She's just waiting for you. Go in after her", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " All right, I live about three blocks down. You guys want to see movies, all right, let's go see movies", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I got these pictures off my dentist. I don't know where be got them. There you are, my friend, that's you", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Doesn't that look like my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah. I wouldn't let my my friend go on a bachelor party", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Are you kidding? What do you think these bachelor parties are for, bachelors? This is for the married men. It's a good excuse to get drunk and find some girls", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I think what I was trying to say was you stick with your night school. Some guys have to make peace with themselves that they're never going to amount to too much. A guy like me. Once I made that peace with myself, I found out it doesn't really matter what you amount to. I got a nice wife and two children I complain about all the time, but if anything ever happened to either one of them, I think I'd die. But you don't have to make that kind of peace, and you'd be crazy to settle for less than what you want. You want something, my friend. I think that's wonderful.  You're a little drunk now, and you're fed up to the teeth. Everybody gets fed up, my friend. You stick with it. You're going to be all right", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Sure. You're a nice guy too", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "... No, I'll kill another hour.... Come on, my friend...", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Okay, I'll see you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't say that. We were matched up, you know. The families kind of agreed on it. I was brought over to her by my mother and father. That's how I met her. She's some kind of tenth cousin. She's all right. She's quiet. I kissed her a couple of times. She just sat there and I kissed her. I think she expected more. She even asked me that. She said to m", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I mean, you think I ought to marry her", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You want me to? All right. I'll go up with you", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'll go up with him. Moral support", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Where you going, my friend", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What th", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It looks like a state hospital", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, it does look a little like a prison", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Here", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'll see you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What am I going to do home? I read all the papers", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Ah, don't go home, my friend. I feel like doing something", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, I want to get home so much to my wife right now I'm going to bust", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Goo", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'll see you, my friend", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'll see you, my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " I love you so much, my friend. I love you so much...", "docId": "Bachelor-Party_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I love you, my friend, I love you, my friend. I love you, my friend ..", "qsentId": 42}]